But as you can imagine,
what they had to do--
I'll just give you one more
example and then we'll stop.
What they had to do is
understand everything
we've just talked about.
How do you engineer the
viscosity, the melting point
to make it all work
in a 3D printer?
The last point I'll
give you is this.
I love this.
This is from a few years ago.
It's a group in Japan
that made a glass that
is as strong as steel.
And what they talk about--
this is what I like.
They say just think of a world
where your smartphone wouldn't
shatter.
OK, cool.
Buildings could be bolstered
against natural disasters, even
cooler.
And then somehow
they bring it down.
Wine glasses are
reassuringly safe.
[LAUGHTER]
Was that really a problem?
I don't know.
And what they did,
fabrication was
conducted using an aerodynamic
levitation furnace where
ingredients were floated
in the air using oxygen gas
and melted together
using CO2 lasers,
and they get a transparent
superglass with 50% alumina.
That was so hard to do
because the aluminum didn't
want to be a glass.
It wanted to go and
become a metal, a crystal.
But by doing it
this way, they were
able to capture it
in the disorder.
All right, have a great night.
See you guys on Friday.